appcraver.com 2010-06-19

# Privacy Statement - iPhone Applications | AppCraver: The Best Apps for iPhone, iPad and iPod touch

For the purposes of this privacy statement, the terms “we”, “us”, “our” and “Appcraver.com” refer to the iPhone Application site AppCraver.com. The terms “You” and “End-User” refer to You as a user of this Site.

Appcraver.com collects no personal information about you when you visit our web site unless otherwise stated or unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, we may collect and store certain information automatically. This information will not be shared with anyone beyond the web site support staff, except when required by law enforcement investigation, and will be used only as a source of anonymous statistical information. This information may include:

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address of the domain from which You access the Internet, either Your individual address or the proxy provided by Your Internet Service Provider (ISP).
  * Date and time You access our site.
  * Pages You view (recorded by the text and graphics files that compose that page).
  * Web address of the site from which You linked directly to our site.
  * Browser version and operating system of the computer You are using.

Appcraver.com is the sole owner of the information collected on the Appcraver.com web site. Appcraver.com collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our site.

We may use the summary statistics to help us make our site more useful to visitors, such as assessing what information is of most and least interest to visitors, and for other purposes such as determining the site’s technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas.

Appcraver.com does not create individual profiles with the information You provide. If information is collected, it will be used solely in connection with Appcraver.com, or for such other purposes as are described at the point of collection. Appcraver.com does not give, sell, or transfer any personal information to any third party.

However, Your e-mail message, question, or comment may be forwarded to other Appcraver.com employees, contractors or subcontractors, who may be better able to help You. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations. However, e-mail and on-line forms are not secure against interception and senders cannot expect privacy.

### **Security**

Appcraver.com follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Forum

If you use any forum or chat feature on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. Appcraver.com also reserves the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in a manner inconsistent with our Terms of Use.

### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you

### “Opting out”

We provide you the opportunity to ’opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you set up an account but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference during signup. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter, by signing into your account or by emailing us at clark (at) appcraver.com

### Legal Disclosure

Appcraver.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our site.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this statement, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
